Guide to the GW Hatchet records, 1904-2007 RG0114
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Hatchet, unbound and bound volumes, 1904-2011; RG0114 Series 6; 32 Linear feet
  - Hatchet Volume 103 (Copy 3), 2006-2007 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 63)
  - Hatchet Volume 104 (Copy 1), May 15, 2007- April 28, 2008; Series 6 (Volume 104 COPY 1)
    1 bound volume, Vol. 104 Iss. 1-59
  - Hatchet Volume 104 (Copy 2), May 15, 2007-April 28, 2008 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 63)
  - Hatchet Volume 105 (Copy 1), May 12, 2008-April 30, 2009; Series 6; 1 vol. (Volume 105 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 105 (Copy 2), May 12, 2008-April 20, 2009 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 63)
  - Hatchet Volume 106 (Copy 1), May 11, 2009-April 26, 2010; Series 6 (Volume 106 COPY 1)
    Scope and Contents
    1 bound volume, and 1 box of loose issues.
  - Hatchet Volume 106 (Copy 2), May 11, 2009-April 26, 2010 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 63)
  - Hatchet Volume 107 (Copy 1), May 10, 2010-April 25,2011; Series 6 (Volume 107 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 107 (Copy 2), May 10, 2010-April 25, 2011 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 64)
  - Hatchet Volume 108 (Copy 1), May 9, 2011-April 30, 2012; 1 vol. (Volume 108 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 108 (Copy 2), May 9, 2011-April 30, 2012 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 65)
  - Hatchet Volume 110, April 28, 2014-April 27, 2015 (Volume 110)
- Hatchet, microfilm, 1904-1989; RG0114 Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet (Reel 1-45)
  This series contains microfilm of the student newspaper. This master set of microfilm of the GW Hatchet date from 1904-89.
  Formery ACC#885
- Photographs and Negatives, 1970 ca. - 1989 ca.; RG0114 Series 8; 6.5 Linear feet (Box 5, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 1, Box 11, Box 10)
  This series contains photographs and negatives. These images cover the dates 1970s-80s. The images are from the files of the GW Hatchet. Subjects of these images include sports including basketball tennis, wrestling, crew, gymnastics, women's sports, golf, baseball, soccer, the hospital, the medical school, campus scenes, buildings including the Academic Center, Marvin Center, Lenthall Houses, Quigley's, dormitories including Thurston Hall, parking lots, individuals such as Jimmy Carter and Ronald Reagan), faculty senate, speakers, commencement, Martha's Marathon, concerts, theater, dances, elections, campus protests, rallies, Gelman Library groundbreaking and donors and Friends of the Libraries, and Aladin).
  Formerly ACC#234
  This series is unprocessed, please ask staff for assistance